<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Beauty. Body. Bliss]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Beauty. Body. Bliss]]></description>
        <link>http://fabfitfree.mom/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 22:31:46 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://fabfitfree.mom/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2018 22:31:45 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[#OneTeam #OneVision #StepUp]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>#OneTeam #OneVision #StepUp</h1>,<h1>Why You. Why Me? Why Now?</h1>,<p>Would you love spending your time with healthy, happy people who are committed to helping people lead healthier happier lives?</p>,<p>Would you like to be the best version of yourself with a healthier mind and body?</p>,<p>Do you have any physical complaints? Are you passionate about healthy, natural solutions?</p>,<p>Would you like to experience consistent energy, lasting fat loss, better sleep, and mental clarity?</p>,<p>Are you interested in slowing down the aging process, or at least looking fabulous and feeling fantastic as each year passes?</p>,<p>Would you like to redesign your lifestyle and make worries about finances something you no longer experience?</p>,<p>Are you positive, fun, and enthusiastic about life?</p>,<p>Would you like to do something every day that makes a positive contribution to the world?</p>,<p>If you answered yes to at least 3 of those questions, truly want to help other people, and are willing to do what it takes to achieve your potential, we would like to invite you to apply for a spot in our group.</p>,<p>Our group’s mission is to free people from physical and financial pain. And with Baby Boomers aging, we have more people that want our help than ever before! This is an amazing time to give people healthy solutions to age and environment related health problems. Let’s face it, Baby Boomers are smart, educated people who want to enjoy an active retirement. They want to stay healthy and energetic to travel the world and play with their grandkids, and we can help. We feel awesome with this nutrition in our bodies. We felt the changes within days of embracing this lifestyle and believe EVERY body deserves to feel this amazing. We’re having fun and making lasting friendships with like-minded people who believe the world CAN be a better place. We know that by getting out of our own comfort zones just a tiny bit to share something that works, we can be part of making our world full of happier, healthier people for whom physical and financial pain is a thing of the past.</p>,<p>If you resonate with any of this, please friend me on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/gayanna" title="g's facebook page">Facebook</a> if we’re not friends yet. Then private message me so we can chat and YOU can decide if one of our solutions is right for you.</p>,<h3><a href="http://justthrive.isagenix.com/en-US/disclaimers" title="Disclaimers">Disclaimers</a></h3>]]></description>
            <link>https://shar.es/1wfjkY</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3e77a863-4099-4b96-b36b-2715f102d766</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 23:52:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>